Thank you, Vegapunk...
for not allowing Ohara's
struggle to be for nothing.
I'm simply well versed in all areas of study.
It's the way of a true scholar.
The shoes are moving on their own!
I can't release you yet.
You'll have to come with me.
There's something I want to show you.
Hey! There's no cockpit
on this thing, Chopper.
Scrap Heap
Fabriophase
Egghead
Scrap Heap
Fabriophase
Egghead
I got it! Maybe this robot...
moves on its own!
Maybe it'll react if we say something to it!
Like... Like...
Move! Move, robot!
It didn't work...
I wonder what the magic word is...
No! It must have a name!
We should call it out!
Move, Robonosuke!
Robo King!
Jeez...
What are you guys, kids?
That obviously won't work.
What?!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
What was that?! Did the robot explode?!
No, it wasn't an explosion.
Then what just happened?!
Hey!
Help me-quasar!
"Quasar"?
Oh no!
I failed again!
Somebody, help me-quasar!
Maybe I warped space-time when I teleported!
Was that old man there before?
I'm sinking! Hey!
I don't think so.
My body's sinking!
Somebody!
I don't know what's going on.
Hey, gramps, do you need help?
Help me-quasar!
What the...?
You're just like Kin'emon.
Hurry up!
I'll get you out!
Thanks!
I knew it!
It's him!
Thank you!
By the way, you're...
Dragon's son, right?
I knew you were here.
I'm glad you came.
And you must be...
Bonney!
You're all grown up!
Vegapunk!
I'm glad to see you doing well!
Old man, are you floating?!
You're wearing them, too.
What?
Those dom shoes have a hover function!
What?! A hover function?!
How do we use it?!
First, press the button on the side...
Oh, this one.
And this lever!
Push it down!
Like this?!
That's it!
We flew too high!
Help me-quasar!
The World's Premier Brain
Head of the Marines' Special Science Group